Guide to the Christopher Knowles Papers, 1973-2015 (bulk 1973-1990) MSS.414
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE: Series II
  - Subseries A: Performances with Christopher Knowles
    - De Hoek Van de Straat 5 "Dialog/Network", 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Emily Likes the TV Poster, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Knot I Land Poster & Program, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - A Letter for Queen Victoria, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Mehdi Khonsari Photos of "A Mad Man, A Mad Dog...", 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Dialog/Curious George Poster, 1980 (Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Performances without Christopher Knowles
    - Byrd Hoffman School of Byrds Programs, 1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Riding the Right Horse Poster, August 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- OVERSIZE: Series III
  - Gavin Brown's Enterprise Posters, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 4 Typings Shown at Gladstone Gallery, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- OVERSIZE: Series IV
  This series contains three bags of color paper cut outs used by Knowles in an exhibit at the Museum Boymans in Rotterdamn. They are listed here as folders 1 through 4 in box 15.
  - Portraits of Christopher by "K.K.", 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Paris Self-Service Story, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - All About Me Book, Song list, 1972, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - David Hatchett Parzival Watercolor, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - History of My Memories, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Get lost Artists Map Downtown New York, c. 2007 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bike Race Print, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Clock Drawing, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Drawings [1 of 2], undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Drawings [2 of2], undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - [Marker Drawing], undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - [Marker Drawings & Songs], undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - [Parzival, song list, birthday drawings], undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - [Pen Drawings], undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Red Ray Stevens, Green Glen Campbell, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Ramsen Street Drawings, water colors and pen drawings, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - [Years and Watercolors], undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Exit Art Labyrinth Wall Typing, February 2009 (Box 13)
  - Apples Peaches Pumpkin Pie Scroll, undated (Box 14)
  - Paper cutouts used at Boymans Exhibit, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Paper cutouts used at Boymans Exhibit, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Paper cutouts used at Boymans Exhibit, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Paper cutouts used at Boymans Exhibit, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - I Got Rhythm, c. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sorry Seems to be the Hardest Word [Song titles], undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - [Yellow, Red, Green Crayon Drawing], undated (Folder 15)
  - New York City's Top 101 of 1967 [Typing on Rice Paper], undated (Folder 16)
- OVERSIZE: Series VI
  - Christopher Knowles & Bob Wilson Press, 1978, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - A Letter for Queen Victoria, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - $ Value of Man press clippings, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Andy Warhol's Interview, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Einstein on the Beach Village Voice, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - A Solo Performance SoHo Weekly News, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Art Communications Edition, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Emily Likes the TV news clippings, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - New York Post Drawing Center Exhibition, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Traveler's Digest Christopher Knowles/Cindy Lubar portrait, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Dialog/Curious George New York Times, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - American Book Review of Typings, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Typings" Press Cards, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Art Forum, 1979, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Parzival New York Times, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Knot I Land Nashville Scene, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - La Tradicion Village Voice, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Art + Auction, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- OVERSIZE: Series VIII
  - Photo portrait of Christopher Knowles, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)